2012年 美国经济崩溃
失业率创新高
犯罪率急剧上升 失去控制 监狱制度出现转折点
所有监狱现被私有企业以牟利为目的开办
终端岛监狱举行一系列死亡竞赛 并在网上直播
囚犯被迫进行生死格斗 节目创下高收视率
他们成为新一批角斗士而终端岛则成为了他们的竞技场
但正如古罗马的暴民一样 观众很快对节目感到厌倦
他们追求更残酷的刺激 死亡飞车也因此诞生
可恶
Damn it!
尾部装甲怎样了?
Rear armor?
毁了
Shot to hell.
你最好后撤
You better drop back...
最后一圈了 我们能赢
It's the last lap. We can win this.
这混球为什么不去死
Why don't this son of a bitch just die?
滑油
Oil.
没了
Out.
烟雾
Smoke.
用完了
Finished.
给我用凝固汽油弹!
Give me the napalm!
什么都用不了!
Nothing works!
把墓碑卸了
Drop the tombstone.
听我指示 三
On my mark. Three,
二
two,
一
one.
混蛋 追上你了
I got you now, motherfucker.
卸!
Mark!
妈的!
Shit!
操!
Fuck!
你要这样玩吗?那好
That's how you want to do it? Okay.
他还在紧追着 我们的油缸爆了
He's still coming. Our tank is exposed.
他追上我们了 你得后撤
He's got us, Frank. You have to drop back.
还有四分之一英里就到终点了 我能赢
It's a quarter mile to the line. I can make it.
再见 弗兰克
Sayonara, Frankie.
弹走
Punch out.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
《死亡飞车》
40年了 比我的婚龄还长
Forty years. Longer than my marriage.
说得好像你会惦记这里
Sounds like you're gonna miss this place.
很难相信这里会倒闭 仅此而已
I still can't believe they closed it down. Just like that.
我只会惦记我的薪水
The only thing I'm gonna miss is my paycheck.
这是老实人干的老实活啊
Well, it was honest work for honest men.
我有一家人要养 在外边又找不到工作
I got a family to feed, and there's no work out there.
我听说码头那边招人
I hear they might be hiring down at the docks.
好像要招五个
Five men, maybe.
谢谢你 哥儿
Hey, thanks, man.
谢谢 杰森
Thanks, Jensen.
拿上你们的薪水尾款 然后离开
Collect your final paycheck and leave.
大门会在15分钟内锁上
The main gate will be locked in 15 minutes.
伙儿 准备被大宰一顿吧
Get ready to be ripped off, boys.
拿上你们的薪水 有秩序地离开工地
Collect your paycheck and leave the premises in an orderly manner.
大门会在15分钟内锁上
The main gate will be locked in 15 minutes.
现金还是支票?
Cash or check?
最好给现金
Better make it cash.
300块
$300.
上两个星期我工作了120个小时
I worked 120 hours the last two weeks.
现金手续费 下一个! 现金手续费?
Cash fee. Next! Cash fee?
你要现金的话 要收手续费
You wanted cash, there's a fee.
那你要支票了吗?
You want a check instead?
看着这家公司倒闭 我才不要
Seeing as the company's out of business, not exactly.
你不满意 那边有投诉信箱 下一个
You don't like it, there's the complaint box. Next!
他们永远不会明白
They never get it.
早就预到有这一天
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
我们都是老实人 跟你们一样!
We're honest workers. We're just like you guys!
你们到底在干什么?
What the hell are you doing here?
你们这群混账
You bastards!
妈的 妈的! 罗斯!
Shit! Shit! Ross!
你没事吧 罗斯?
You okay, Ross?
塑胶子弹 那群混蛋!
Rubber bullets, the assholes!
来啊!
Come on!
嗨 亲爱的
Hi, honey.
嗨 对不起 那么迟
Hi. Sorry I'm so late.
工作愉快吗?
Nice day at work?
还好
Yeah. Just fine.
把衬衣给我
Give me that shirt.
他们叫来防暴警察 情况很恶劣
They called the riot police. It got ugly.
我配不上你
I don't deserve you.
杰森·艾姆斯 你是个好人
You're a good man, Jensen Ames.
除了我 别人怎么看你都不重要
And it doesn't matter what anyone else thinks but me.
那 300块 他们就给了我这么多
So, $300. That's all they gave us.
我们能撑下去的 我们一直都能
We'll make it last. We always do.
我明天开始找工作
I'll start looking tomorrow.
我想你忘记了我嫁给你
I think you're forgetting that I married you
为的不是钱啊
for your non-financial assets.
那现在呢?
Did you now?
爸爸回家了 声音是你发出的吗?
Daddy's home. Is it you who was making all that noise?
小派帕想要什么 要听故事吗?
What does little Piper want? Want a story?
你知道你不会明白
You know you won't understand it.
但我可以好好练习 那很好啊
But it will be good practice for me. But it will be good practice for me.
管他呢
What the hell.
我们疯狂一回
Let's go crazy.
闻起来味道不错哦
Something smelIs good.
亲爱的?
Honey?
苏西?
Suzy?
趴在地上 趴在地上
Stay on the ground! Stay on the ground.
把刀放下
Drop the knife!
别反抗 趴在地上
Do not resist! Stay on the ground!
趴在原地!
Stay where you are!
趴在地上!
Stay on the ground!
别动!
Don't move!
走
Move.
靠着墙边
Get up against the wall.
自己擦身
Scrub yourself.
停下
Stop.
囚犯退后
Prisoner will step back.
节日快乐
Happy holidays.
他们滑倒了
They slipped.
早上好 早
Good morning. Morning.
狱长 早
Morning, Warden.
早
Morning.
早上好 夫人
Good morning, ma'am.
早上好
Good morning.
那是场里最翘的屁股
There goes the baddest ass in the yard.
哥儿 你像是爱上她了
Sound like you're in love, homie.
我是
I am.
妈的 我起来就为了吃这个?
Damn. I had to wake up for this?
是我的幻觉?
All right, is it my imagination,
还是这狗屎越来越烂了?
or is this shit getting worse?
像这坨 到底是什么?
Like, what is this supposed to be?
燕麦片
Oatmeal.
我觉得是
I think.
哥儿 你怎么吃得消燕麦片?
Man, how do you fuck up oatmeal?
那个新来的是谁?
Who's the new guy?
杰森·艾姆斯
Jensen Ames.
那个车手?
The driver?
从没听说过他
Never heard of him.
对了 我数年前看过他赛车 他车技很好
Oh, yeah, I saw him race years ago. He's good.
后来搬去了州北地区
Did some time upstate.
也因此毁了他的职业生涯
Killed his career.
威拉德赛 联盟赛和巴特勒赛的 最快圈速保持者
Holder of the fastest laps at Willard, Union and Butler.
希望他在赛道下跟在赛道上一样快
I hope he's as fast off the track as he is on.
日子从不平淡
Never a dull day.
我们撤
Let's get the fuck out of here.
小心 是派晨高
Heads up. It's Pachenko.
你就是那个杀妻凶手
So you're the wife killer.
杀死一个女人需要莫大的勇气啊
Takes a big man to kill a woman.
我猜你也强奸幼童吧
I suppose you rape kiddies, too.
各位 听到吗?
You hear that, everyone?
他杀女人 强奸幼童
Guy kilIs women. Rapes kiddies.
你们觉得我们该怎么处理这事情?
What do you think we ought to do about that?
趴在地上 趴在地上 快点!
Get down on the ground! Down on the ground! Now!
谁也别动!
Nobody move!
我猜他也不喜欢燕麦片
I guess he didn't like the oatmeal, either.
你麻烦惹大了
Well, you've got stones.
把一个兄弟会的头头打伤
Putting the hurt on a Brotherhood general.
但现在 麻烦还在后头呢
But right now, that's the least of your problems.
跟车手有关的人 狱长都不会对他们客气
The warden does bad things to people that mix it up with the drivers.
囚犯77119 夫人
Prisoner 77119, ma'am.
谢谢 里奇先生
Thank you, Mr. Ulrich.
这座监狱是杀人犯
This prison is the home to murderers,
强奸犯和各种暴力罪犯的家园
rapists and violent offenders of every kind.
美国刑罚体制把人渣中的人渣交给我
The United States penal system sends me the worst of the worst.
但你刚才惹怒的那个人...
But the men you've provoked...
这样说吧 艾姆斯先生
Well, let's just say, Mr. Ames,
你在这里的小命
that the life term you joined us for
或许比你想象中要短得多
may be a lot shorter than you think.
我明白 惯例啊
I understand. Tradition.
令新人受挫 所有人都享受过这种爽逼好时光
Soften up the new guy. An ass-slapping good time had by all.
对于我
Foul language is an issue
脏话是个问题
for me.
查看你的记录时
While looking over your record,
我不禁留意了你的工作经历
I couldn't help noticing your occupational history.
看来你有点赛车才华
It seems you have some talent behind the wheel.
出于好奇问问 你最后一次赛车是几时?
Out of curiosity, when was the last time you raced?
有一段时间了 我驾照没了
It's been a while. I lost my license.
如果我能帮你怎么样?
What if I could help you?
把驾照搞回来?
Get my license back?
我脑子想的是另一回事
I had something else in mind.
你知道死亡飞车
You're familiar with the Death Race
和那个叫弗兰克斯坦的车手吗?
and the driver the fans call Frankenstein?
一个因撞车而面容全毁
A man so disfigured by crashes
以致他被迫戴上面具的人
that he's forced to wear a mask.
人们热切期待他能重回赛道
His return to the track is highly anticipated,
而这就是我的问题所在
and therein lies my problem.
还没有人知道 可怜的弗兰克已经死了
No one knows yet, but poor Frank died
在最后一场比赛过后不久 他死于手术台上
on an operating table not long after his last race.
谁都可以戴上面具
Anyone can wear the mask.
但不是谁都能开车
But not just anyone can drive the car.
你车技精湛我要求你把传奇延续下去
You have the skilIs I require to keep the legend alive.
我要你成为弗兰克
I want you to become Frankenstein.
不 谢谢了
No, thanks.
他死了
He's dead.
为什么你不把真相说出来?
Why don't you just tell the truth?
观众想再次看到弗兰克
The audience wants to see Frank again.
他令他们感动 他鼓舞了他们
He moves them. Inspires them.
在这个世界里 这样的人不是那么容易找到的
And in this world, that's not so easy to come by.
是什么让你认为
What makes you think for a second
我会赌命为你做这事?
I would risk my life doing this for you?
赢过五场比赛
Win five races,
你就自由了
you go free.
那是规矩
Those are the rules.
弗兰克已经赢了四场
And Frank has won four.
再赢一场
Win one more,
你就可以走了
you walk.
管这叫直觉吧 但是...
Call it intuition, but...
我觉得你不属于这里
I don't think you belong in here
跟那帮禽兽待在一起
with the rest of these animals.
恐怕我会让你失望
I might surprise you.
比赛周五举行 我要你做决定
The race is Friday, and I need your decision.
10秒钟后 我会收回这个提议
Ten seconds from now, I will retract this offer,
把它转给囚犯68815 詹姆斯·弗朗西斯·巴里尼
and extend it to Prisoner 68815, James Francis Barlini,
他水平没你那么高
who, clearly not of your caliber,
但他对此必定满腔热情
will be quite enthusiastic about it.
而你 就很不幸要独自度过的你监狱生涯
And you, unfortunately, will need to spend your incarceration in solitary.
从现在起我知道你的肮脏小秘密了
Since now I know your dirty little secret.
我肯定你宁愿单独监禁
I'm sure you'll find solitary preferable
想想派晨高先生和他的朋友们 会怎么对付你
to what Mr. Pachenko and his friends have in mind for you.
你是位技术精湛的车手 你机会很大
You're a skilled driver. Your chances are good.
埃姆斯先生 我是在还你自由
I'm offering you your freedom, Mr. Ames.
如果这都不值得赌命 还有什么值得?
If it's not worth risking your life for, what is?
好 把她升起 把线缝紧 她内出血
All right, turn her up and tighten the lines! She's hemorrhaging!
夫人
Ma'am.
你不必叫我"夫人" 你知道的
You don't have to call me "ma'am." You know that.
这是埃姆斯先生 你知道他为何而来
This is Mr. Ames. You know why he's here.
噢 我不知道
Oh, I do now.
离比赛还不到一个星期
The race is less than a week away.
我对你充满信心
I have great confidence in you.
那么 我走了 你们两个互相熟悉一下
Well, then, I'll leave you two to get acquainted.
杰森·格纳·艾姆斯 24岁搬到美国
Jensen Garner Ames. Moved to the States at 24 years old.
名字源于"杰森拦截机"这款车
Named after a car, the Jensen Interceptor.
三次获得本地跑道赛冠军
A three-time local speedway champion.
是你做足功课了 还是因为你无所不知?
You've done your homework. Or do you just know everything?
杰森拦截机 我有一台
Jensen Interceptor. I had one.
开起来像台校巴
Handled like a school bus.
管我叫教练 大家都这么叫我
Call me Coach. Everyone does.
炮手和管事婆
Gunner. Lists.
这是弗兰克
This is Frank.
带你周围看看
I'll show you around.
我们有个功能完善的车间
We have a fully functioning auto shop,
跟监狱外的一样
just like you'd find in the outside world.
每支车队都有各自的车间
Each team has their own shop.
我们河水不犯井水
We don't help them. They don't help us.
在那些囚犯面前 你是杰森·艾姆斯 新来的油猴
To the inmates, you're Jensen Ames, the new grease monkey.
除了车队中的我们和一部分狱警
Nobody will know you're Frank except us on the team
没人会知道你是弗兰克
and a handful of the guards.
没人会说出来
Nobody will talk.
你怎能那么肯定?
How can you be so sure?
轩尼诗 她是这里的审判官 陪审员和执行官
Hennessey. In here, she is judge, jury and executioner.
车赛是她的心肝宝贝 她会干掉任何威胁到车赛的人
The race is her baby. Anyone who threatens it, she kills.
弗兰克离开赛道后
The audience for the race has halved
观众的数量已经减半
since Frank's been out of the game,
公司的利润也一样
and so has the corporation's profit.
那就是她需要你的原因
That's why she needs you.
后面的是什么?
What's back there?
问得好
That's a good question.
轩尼诗把狱里一整个联隔离了一个月
Hennessey's had a whole wing of the prison in isolation for a month.
要他们为某种东西埋头苦干
Working on something.
是时候见见这头怪物了
Time to meet the Monster.
野马V8长顶赛车
Mustang V8 Fastback.
取自最好 把它改得更好
Took the best and made it better.
那是台5.4升鲁斯V8引擎 装有福特竞赛超级增压器
That's a V8 Roush 5.4 liter with a Ford Racing supercharger
能爆发出850匹马力和接近
putting out 850 horsepower and close to...
700磅扭力
Seven hundred pounds of torque
配有连续多缸喷油系统
with sequential multi-port fuel injection.
貌似还有一套250匹马力的 氮气装置
Looks like there's a 250 hp NOS unit.
以防万一
Just in case.
接着是我们乐于为你 度身定做的保护套件
Then we had some fun customizing your personal protection package.
前部和侧部是0.75英寸厚的钢板
Three-quarter inch steel plate, front and sides.
这里 这里和那里是防弹玻璃
Bulletproof glass will be here, here and there.
后部是6英寸厚的实心护甲 我们称它为
And in the rear, a six-inch solid steel shield we call
墓碑
"the tombstone."
防御用的滑油 烟雾和凝固汽油弹
Oil, smoke, and napalm for defense.
攻击用的双30毫米口径弹药带式机关枪
And twin 30-millimeter belt-fed machine guns for offense.
弹药呢?
So where's the ammo?
车赛当天才有
We get that on race day.
可惜
Pity.
对 每个人第一次看到它都这么想
Yeah. Everyone thinks that, first time.
怎么想?
Thinks what?
想把枪对着狱警 想逃狱
About turning the guns on the guards, about escaping.
不 我不是在想这个
No, I wasn't thinking that.
我很高兴 因为
Well, I'm glad, because
轩尼诗在所有车的枪里都装上了
Hennessey has got electric kill switches
电击开关
in all the guns in all the cars.
所有瞭望塔都全副武装
And all the guard towers are fortified,
他们的枪比你的还要猛
and their guns are bigger than your guns.
我有提到那些直升机吗?
But did I mention the helicopters,
还有我们正处于一座岛上
and also the fact that we're on an island here
离最近的海岸线有一英里远
a mile from the nearest shoreline?
这里唯一的进出口
The only way in or out of here
是你进来时那条狭窄的桥
is on that one skinny bridge you came in on.
那是什么?
What's that?
车最重要的部分
Most important part of the car.
弗兰克杀了多少人?
How many people has Frank killed?
20 每场比赛的死亡率是62.2%
Twenty. The mortality rate is average 62.2% per race.
那么弗兰克四次战胜厄运
So Frank beat the odds four times.
对 直到他们打败他
Yeah. Till they beat him.
车赛分三场在三天里举行
The race takes place in three stages over three days.
在头两场
The first two stages,
你必须去干掉
you just got to try and get rid of
尽可能多的对手
as much of the competition as you can
同时保住性命到达终点
while getting your own skinny ass over the line alive.
第三场才比速度
Third stage is where speed counts.
谁先到达终点谁赢
First one over that line wins.
明天早上你会见到你的领航员 凯斯
Tomorrow morning, you meet your navigator, Case.
她会帮你引航路线 装载武器
She'll help you navigate the course, reload your weapons
和车辆运行这方面的东西
and help with the running of the car.
我想开赛之前跟她谈谈
I'd like to talk to her ahead of time, before the race.
是啊我也想有个大波妹
Yeah. I'd like a big-tittie girl
替我舔舔鞋子上的花生酱
to lick peanut butter off my toes.
但不可能
That ain't gonna happen.
哥儿 这里毕竟是座监狱 她是条小妞
It's still a prison, man. She's a chick.
他们从州北部的女子监狱坐狱车过来
They get bussed in from the women's facility upstate.
一切都关于收视率 飙车和美女
It's all about ratings, fast cars, pretty women.
对 大炮乔是唯一一个用 男领航员的车手
Yeah, Machine Gun Joe is the only one that has a male navigators.
因为他是个同性恋
'Cause he's gay.
实际上 他超车超得太快了
Actually, it's 'Cause he goes through them so fast,
连观众都看得头晕
the audience gets squeamish.
对 他超他们车 超他们的屁眼
Yeah, he goes through them. Through their ass.
每杀一个人 他都在这里割一刀留所纪念
He cuts each kill into his skin as a souvenir, right here.
其他车手呢?
What about the rest of the drivers?
管事婆?
Lists?
14K
14K.
第一代美籍华人 第十代三合会会员
First generation Chinese-American, 10th generation Triad.
他父亲送他上商学院
And his father sent him to business school.
他是这里唯一一个 拿到麻省理工学位的人
He's the only man in here who holds a degree from MIT.
他在赛道外杀了四个人
He's killed four men off the track.
我们都知道
That we know of.
在赛道上杀了七个
Another seven on it.
死神 赫特·格林
Hector Grimm, The Grimm Reaper.
他是位大师 心理变态
The man's a master. Clinical psychopath.
他相信轩尼诗是
Believes that Hennessey is an avatar
印度死神迦梨的化身
of the Hindu goddess of death, Kali,
而他就是她的使徒
and that he is her messenger.
飞越疯人院
Cuckoo.
被判三倍终身监禁
Three time consecutive life sentences.
他在赛道外杀了6个人 赛道上杀了12个
He's killed six men off the track, another 12 on it.
你已经见过兄弟会的本地分部了
You've already met the local chapter of the Brotherhood.
他们的车手 派晨高 在赛道上杀了9个人
Their driver, Pachenko, has killed nine men on the track.
没人知道他在赛道外杀了多少个
Nobody knows how many off.
崔维斯·柯尔特 本地巨星
Travis Colt, our local superstar.
当过全美汽车比赛协会车手
Used to race for NASCAR.
是 他也很棒
Yeah, he was good, too.
直到他喝了一瓶苏格兰威士忌 和一把安眠酮
Until he fell asleep behind the wheel of his Mercedes
在他的大奔里睡着了
with the help of a bottle of scotch and a handful of ludes.
把斯卡拉歌剧院的整个露台铲平了
Wiped out the entire patio of La Scala.
把12人送进医院
Sent a dozen people to the hospital.
他妈的!
God damn it!
死了3个
It killed three of them.
技术上说 他是这里最好的车手
Technically the best driver in here,
但内心却是一头禽兽
but a mean son of a bitch within.
娘儿
Ladies.
我听说你们的弗兰克还在病床上 有十五处未愈合骨折
I hear your man Frank is still in the infirmary with 15 unhealed fractures.
我还听说他不能参赛了
I also hear he's not gonna make the race.
你听到得可真多
You hear a lot.
这新来的是谁?
Who's the new fish?
油猴
Grease monkey.
好啊猴儿
Well, well. Monkey.
我给你改个新名字
I got a new name for you.
丑八怪
Igor.
因为你是狱里最臭的怪胎
'Cause you about the ugliest motherfucker in this prison, yo.
好笑吗?
Funny, huh?
见到弗兰克的时候告诉他
You tell Frank when you see him.
这是我们之间的比赛
This race is between me and him.
这次不再是进医院那么简单
This time won't be no infirmary.
这次进的是太平间
It'll be the morgue.
我会把话传给他
I'll be sure to pass it on.
我们撤
Let's get out of here, man.
伙儿 他真是个愤怒的同性恋啊
Man, that is one angry homo.
他们是谁?
Who are they?
工作组
Work detail.
为了获得行为分 在赛道上工作
Get to work on the track for good behavior.
那些是全球定位手镯
Those are GPS tracking bracelets.
以防他们跳河逃跑
In case somebody decides to go for a swim.
戒指
The ring.
这是老弗兰克的
This was the old Frank's.
已经跟他的手融为一体
It kind of melted to his hand.
弗兰克斯坦!
Frankenstein!
弗兰克斯坦 弗兰克斯坦!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
弗兰克斯坦 弗兰克斯坦! 弗兰克斯坦 弗兰克斯坦!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein! Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
混球
Assholes.
把他交给你们
He's all yours.
别跟其他车手说话
Don't talk to the other drivers.
弗兰克从不说话 制造一种神秘感
Frank never did. Part of the mystique.
让面具替你说话
Let the mask do the work.
麻烦来了
Here comes trouble.
我们的小妞来了
There's our girl.
我是凯斯
I'm Case.
弗兰克
Frank.
有趣 听起来不像弗兰克啊
Funny, you don't sound like Frank.
别慌 我知道
Don't sweat it. I know.
我跟弗兰克一起比赛过 我会帮你看着的
I drove with Frank. I'll watch your back.
希望你帮我看得更好
Better than you watched his, I hope.
还在这里 我得赶紧一点
Still here. Well, I guess I got to work a little harder.
囚犯 上车
Get back to your car, prisoner.
你确定你知道怎样交朋友吗?
You sure know how to make friends.
凯斯 这是反光玻璃
Case. This is mirrored glass.
看不到里面的 你可以把面具脱下
No one can see in, so you might want to take the mask off.
除非你喜欢戴着
Unless you like it under there.
他这么能戴着那玩意开车?
How the hell did he drive in that thing?
什么?
What?
你比上个弗兰克好看
You're better looking than the last Frank.
但撞过几次车就不同了
A few crashes should change that.
挂档
Start the transmission.
3 2 1
Three, two, one.
我们全球直播
And we're live worldwide.
欢迎收看死亡飞车
Welcome to Death Race.
终端岛监狱将举办为期三天的
Terminal Island Penitentiary hosts three days
汽车终极大屠杀
of the ultimate in auto carnage.
第一场比赛将在10分钟内开始
Stage 1 of the race begins streaming live in 10 minutes.
现在订购第一场只需要99块
Subscribe to Stage 1 now for $99,
订购全三场超低价只需250块
or subscribe to all three stages for the low price of $250.
100多台实况镜头为你直播
Access to over 100 live camera feeds.
零距离观看你最喜爱的车手
Watch from the car of your favorite driver.
你爱怎么看就怎么看 不经审查 不经剪辑
See the action your way, uncensored and unedited.
一场全速死亡之旅
A full-on fight to the death,
为你带来四场赢家弗兰克斯坦
featuring four-time winner Frankenstein.
三场赢家大炮乔
Three-time winner Machine Gun Joe.
派晨高
Pachenko.
崔维斯·柯尔特
Travis Colt.
观众大爱弗兰克斯坦
Audience favorite Frankenstein
将延续他与大炮乔的
resumes his bitter grudge match
怨恨仇杀
with Machine Gun Joe.
缺席六个月后 弗兰克重新回到赛场上
Frankenstein returns to the track after a six-month absence.
观众想念他
They've missed him.
他就是个不死之躯
He's the man that just won't die.
1200万观众只观看他的镜头
Twelve million hits on his angle alone.
他还没发动引擎呢
He hasn't even started the engine.
今天我们有4500万观众
We'll do 45 million viewers today.
你为什么被关进来?
So, what are you in for?
他们说我杀了一警察
They say I killed a cop.
你有杀吗?
Did you do it?
有
Yeah.
坏警察?
Bad cop?
好警察
Good cop.
差劲的丈夫
Lousy husband.
弗兰克 凯斯 听到我说吗?
Frank, Case, you read me?
听到
We hear you.
这场比赛跑三圈
This is a three-lap race.
轩尼诗在第二圈才会激活武器
Hennessey doesn't activate the weapons till lap two.
记住先到先得
Now remember, it's first come, first served,
所以排前有好处
so it pays to be out in front.
好了 倒数
This is it. Countdown.
你肯定他能做到?
You're sure he can deliver?
向左推进100英尺
Jog left to 100 feet.
50 20...
50, 20...
冲!
Now!
加速 左路猛超!
Punch it! Hard left up ahead.
看来他自己能应付
He seems to be handling himself.
醒醒!
Wakey-wakey!
我们被超了 你得追上!
We're being passed. We've gotta catch up!
我知道我在干什么!
Man, I know what I'm doing!
嘿 就别管那混球...
Hey, just leave that motherfucker...
闭嘴!
Shut up, man!
我知道我在干什么
I know what the hell I'm doing.
你想怎样?
What you gonna do?
你不能跟乔这样子并排走
You can't go head-to-head with Joe like this.
他会撞散你
He'll tear you apart.
听到吗?
You read me?
在你害死我们之前 听他说
Listen to him, before you get us both killed.
凯斯 帮他解决
Case, help him out of there!
左边有条捷径
There's a shortcut to the left.
那边!
There!
他在抄捷径!
He's taking the shortcut!
你以为我看不见吗?
You don't think I see that?
激活宝剑和护盾
Activate swords and shields.
宝剑触发主要的枪弹
The swords arm the main guns.
护盾触发凝固汽油弹 滑油和烟雾
Shields trigger the napalm, oil and smoke.
我知道 我以前看过这车赛
I know. I've seen this race before.
你自以为是 需要整台车的重量才能触发的
You think you know. It takes the weight of the entire car.
你必须四个轮子都同时碰到按钮
You have to make contact with all four tires simultaneously.
还有什么我不知道的吗?
Anything else I'm missing?
别要我多说
Don't get me started.
激活骷髅
Activate death heads.
骷髅激活了
Death heads activated.
爽吧 宝贝!
Feel it, baby!
宝贝 死神又得一分了
Score another one for the Reaper, baby.
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气 来吧 解除警报
Don't mention it. Come on. All clear.
操你妈的贱逼 我操!
Fuck you, puto! Fuck you!
我们有枪了
We got guns.
小心 滑油
Look out. Oil.
妈的!
Damn!
你老妈是个贱逼 混球!
Your mother's a puta, motherfucker!
什么?
What the fuck?
我们得返回比赛
We got to get back in the race.
准备飞弹
开火!
知道我叫什么吗?
我叫14K啊
宝贝 我是他妈的死神
I'm the fucking Reaper, baby.
杀不死我的
Can't kill me.
你们可以烧我
You can burn me.
可以射我 但就他妈的杀不死我
You can fucking shoot me, but you just can't motherfucking kill me!
下次比赛前把窗口擦干净
Get that off my window when we get back.
夫人 收视率直飙4600万
We're streaming to 46 million viewers, ma'am.
攻击武器准备好
Offensive weapons are up.
启动了
It's on.
操 卡住了
Fuck. It's jammed.
掩护我
Cover me.
老天爷!
Jesus Christ!
抓紧 凯斯!
Hold tight, Case!
我回来了
I'm back.
谢谢 不客气
Thank you. My pleasure.
前面有护盾!
Shield up ahead!
那狗娘养的!
That son of a bitch!
他从柯尔特手上抢了护盾!
He just stole a shield from Colt!
防御武器启动
Defense weapons are on.
给他尝尝
Let him have it.
凝固汽油弹不能发射!
The napalm won't fire!
烟雾
Smoke.
没烟雾 没滑油 没凝固汽油弹?
No smoke? No oil? No napalm?
又没有了?
Again?
操!
Fuck, man.
记得我吗 混球?
Remember me, motherfucker?
教练!
Coach!
墓碑快承受不了了
The tombstone won't take much more of this.
弗兰克 凯斯 那些20口径子弹
Frank, Case, those 50 caliber shelIs will be through the tombstone
会瞬间射穿墓碑的
in a matter of seconds.
我的建议是 要么输给他 要么干掉他
My advice, either lose him or kill him.
解下凝固汽油弹
Unhook the napalm.
坐在我大腿上
Get on my lap.
什么?
What?
坐在我大腿上
Get on my lap.
搞什么?
What the hell?
圣诞快乐 混蛋!
Merry Christmas, asshole!
妈的!
Oh, shit!
漂亮
Nice work.
他要去哪里?
Where's he going?
抄捷径 加速 我们能赢他
A shortcut. Punch it. We can beat him.
小心!
Look out!
格林 柯尔特和西亚德都丧生了 6位车手生还
Grimm, Colt and Siad are gone. Six remaining drivers alive.
现在就订购第二场比赛
Subscribe to Stage 2 now!
先生们 还有14个小时 我们开工
We have 14 hours, gentlemen, so let's get to work.
从这里开始
Starting with this.
凯斯 发生什么事了?
So what happened out there, Case?
他分心了
He got distracted.
他分心了?
He got distracted?
教练!
Coach!
什么?
What?
看看 喷油器好好的啊
Look at this. The oil sprayers work fine.
真见鬼
Well, I'll be damned.
站住
Stop.
最后一名
Last place.
太烂了
It's too bad.
向好的方面看
Look on the bright side.
人们都喜欢看英雄回归
Everyone loves a comeback.
有什么能帮你的吗 艾姆斯先生?
What can I do for you, Mr. Ames?
你真幸运 一个像我这样的车手
You sure are lucky a driver like me
碰巧出现在你的监狱里
just happened to turn up in your prison when I did.
不仅是幸运
Oh, I'm more than lucky.
我是被眷顾着
I'm blessed.
有时就好像是上帝之手
Sometimes it's like the right hand of God
总是放在我肩膀上
is sitting on my shoulder.
我明天不参赛
I'm not racing tomorrow.
去你的
Go fuck yourself.
等等
Wait.
把他的手铐解下
Take his shackles off.
你可以回避一下 里奇先生
Please excuse us, Mr. Ulrich.
詹姆斯先生也回避一下
And take Mr. James with you.
你认得这些人吗?
Do you recognize these people?
你女儿会认得
Because your daughter will.
他们是她的养父母
They're her new parents.
她叫什么名字?
What's her name?
派帕
Piper.
她长大后会管这个人叫爸爸
That's the man she'll grow up calling Daddy.
除非你采取点措施
Unless you do something about it.
她现在在哪里?
Where is she now?
我肯定我把地址放在这里某个地方
Oh, I'm sure I have her address around here somewhere.
你是个聪明人 艾姆斯先生
You're a smart man, Mr. Ames.
按我的游戏规则玩 皆大欢喜
Play my game, we both go home happy.
杀死我妻子的人也在这监狱里
The man who killed my wife is in this prison.
我想知道当面对质时 他会怎么答我
I wonder what he'll say when I ask him why he did it.
为什么你不照照镜子 问问镜中人?
Why don't you look in a mirror? Ask him.
可怜的派帕 她的爸爸杀死了她的妈妈
Poor Piper. It must be hard growing up with that knowledge.
背负着这一耻辱长大可真不好受
That your father killed your mother.
你要一头怪物
You wanted a monster.
那好 现在你有了
Well, you've got one.
她的眼睛像你
She has your eyes.
像她妈妈
Her mother's.
教练 为什么你没有编号的?
So why don't you wear a number, Coach?
因为我不是囚犯
Because I'm not a prisoner.
三年前我获准假释
I qualified for parole three years ago.
当我走到大门时...
Got as far as the gate.
他们称它为"某某综合症"
They got a name for it, something-or-other syndrome.
事实是 我来这里后 这世界已经改变了
The simple fact is, the world's changed since I've been in here.
那个世界 我不认识 也不太想去认识 但这里?
Don't know it. Don't much want to. But this?
我熟悉这里
This I know.
- 他们用什么借口关你进来? - 多得是
- What did they send you away for? - Oh, plenty.
但无一成立
And nothing.
你是怎么被关进来的?
To what do we owe the pleasure of your company?
我杀了我妻子
I killed my wife.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你是条狠汉 但你不会杀你妻子
You're a hard man, but you ain't no wife killer.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
我亲眼见过那种人
I've met my share.
但你 你看着你女儿的眼神
But you, the way you looked at her...
如果你杀了她妈妈 你不可能那样子望着她 所以...
You couldn't do that if you'd killed her mother. So...
我说你在胡扯
I say bullshit.
教练
Coach.
如果我说轩尼诗杀了我妻子 然后嫁祸给我
What would you say if I told you Hennessey had my wife killed
把我关在这里 成为她的弗兰克斯坦
and me framed for it
你会怎么看?
so she could bring me in here to be her Frankenstein?
我这么胡扯的话 你会怎么看?
What would you say to that bullshit?
她叫苏西
Her name was Suzy.
我就知道 我有这么一天
I was always headed here. Always knew.
但她不知道
She didn't.
她是我新生活的希望
She was my chance at something else.
但那婊子从我身边夺走了她
And that bitch took her away from me.
"并使你的日子在
"That thy days may be long upon the land...
耶和华你神所赐的地上得以长久"
which the Lord thy... Giveth thee."
"你不可...
"Thou shalt not...
杀人"
kill."
你得休息一下 睡个觉
You should take a break. Get some sleep.
我很好 管事婆
I'm okay, Lists.
集中精神去比赛
Concentration for the race.
你需要的是集中精神 你得去休息一下
Concentration, that's what you need. Gotta get your rest.
或许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
毕竟我还是要休息的
I will take that break after all.
好主意
Good call.
那家伙完全不会打磨
Guy can't grind for shit.
走开!
Move!
找我吗?
Looking for me?
按住他
Hold him.
你杀死我妻子
You killed my wife.
或许是我干的
Well, now, maybe I did.
我不在乎那婊子是不是要
I don't care if the queen bitch
留着你比赛
wants to save you for the track.
没有一个对兄弟会不敬的人能活着
Nobody disrespects the Brotherhood and lives.
放下他
Put him down.
我要砸掉你的头
I'm going to take your head.
他妈的!
What the fuck!
轩尼诗指使我做的 里奇...
Hennessey made me do it. Ulrich...
还有里奇
Ulrich too.
放过我
Let me go, man.
要我做什么我都愿意
I'll do anything.
你要死在这里
You're going to die here.
操你妈!
Fuck you!
小伙 冷静
Now, now, boys.
留着力气比赛吧 好吗?
Let's save that for the track, huh?
教练!
Coach!
来看看这里
Take a look at this.
他们究竟在这里建造什么?
What the hell were they building in here?
很快就会知道
We'll find out soon enough.
囚犯!
Prisoner!
是时候出发了
It's time to get ready.
欢迎收看死亡飞车第二场
Welcome to the next installment of Death Race.
第二场即将开始
Stage 2 begins.
格林 柯尔特和西亚德都丧生了
Grimm, Colt and Siad are gone.
剩下六名车手
Six remaining drivers alive.
14K
14K.
派晨高
Pachenko.
里金斯
Riggins.
卡森
Carson.
三场赢家大炮乔
Three-time winner Machine Gun Joe.
排最后一名的是他的死敌 弗兰克斯坦
And starting from the back of the grid, his archrival, Frankenstein.
这可能是我们最后一次看到 弗兰克斯坦比赛
This could be the last time we see Frankenstein race.
再赢一场他就重获到自由
Just one more victory and he wins his freedom.
前提是乔不先把他干掉
If Joe doesn't kill him first.
超过5000万观众已经订购节目
Over 50 million viewers have already subscribed.
千万别错过这场史诗之战 现在就订购第二场吧
Don't miss this epic battle. Subscribe to Stage 2, now.
集中精神
Pay attention!
他在哪里?
Where is he?
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
他在干嘛?
What's he doing?
他落在后面 他压根没打算比赛
He's dropping back. He's not even trying to race.
我们要谈谈
We're gonna have a little talk.
出隧道前 就可以把事情说完
We're gonna be done by the time we leave the tunnel.
你是不是杀了老弗兰克?
Did you kill the old Frank?
什么?
What?
很快就到隧道了
Tunnel comes up fast.
记得那个凝固汽油弹筒的事故吗?
Remember what happened to the napalm canister?
如果发生在你身上 那可真令人惋惜
Be a real shame for that to happen to you.
你是不是杀了老弗兰克?
Did you kill the old Frank?
我毁坏了他的尾部武器
I sabotaged his rear weapons.
为什么?
Why?
轩尼诗
Hennessey.
她答应会签署释放令 那是我重获新生的机会
She said she'd sign my release papers. It's my life back.
要是我 我也会杀他
I'd have killed him, too.
我没有杀他!
I didn't kill him!
他不肯放弃 我只是要保证他不能赢
He wouldn't quit. I just wanted to make sure he didn't win.
为什么轩尼诗要那样做?
Why would Hennessey want that?
把弗兰克留着这里 比赛
To keep Frank here, racing.
那昨天呢?
And yesterday?
她要我拖后你
She wanted me to set you back.
所以她也不给我赢
So I'm not supposed to win, either.
就是为了让比赛更刺激
Just make it exciting.
我想知道的就这些
That's all I wanted to know.
坐稳
Hold tight.
加油 全速前进!
Come on! Just come on through!
妈的!
Damn!
他跟着派晨高
He's going after Pachenko.
前面有宝剑和护盾 拿防御
Sword and shield ahead. Take defense.
不
No.
我要杀一个人
There's someone I need to kill.
你跑在前头了
You're out in front.
你还打算射谁?
Who are you going to shoot at?
你死定了!
You're a dead man!
我叫你拿防御的了
I told you to take defense!
他的装备太猛了
He's too heavily armored!
操!
Fuck!
放烟雾
Hit the smoke.
你在比赛 你不能往后倒的
This is a race. You don't go backwards.
你不能下车的
And you don't get out of the car.
轩尼诗指使的 轩尼诗
It was Hennessey. Hennessey.
我知道 下一个是她
I know. She's next.
收到 弗兰克下了车
I got it. Frank's out of his car.
什么?
What?
他下车了
He stepped out of his car.
好 看到了 我要武器
Okay. I see him. I need guns.
好 前面50码有宝剑
Yes. Sword coming up in 50 yards.
怎么了? 我不知道
What happened? I don't know.
一定是谁拿了
Somebody must have grabbed it.
什么意思 有人拿了?
What do you mean, somebody grabbed it?
哥儿 我以为它是亮着的
Look, man. I thought it was lit.
什么意思啊你以为?
What do you mean, you thought?
从我的车滚出去
Man, get the fuck out of my car.
什么?
What?
我说 从我的车滚出去!
I said, get the fuck out of my car!
妈的 拜托 不要!
Oh, hell, no! Come on, man.
听着 我们...等等 等等!
Listen, we got... Wait! Wait! Wait!
等等 还没轮到我 这不是我的职责!
Wait! Wait! It ain't my turn! It's not what I do.
进去
Get in there.
小伙 别让我失望
Don't let me down, boy.
出动无畏舰
Release the Dreadnought.
教练?
Coach?
噢
Oh.
现在我知道他们在建造什么了
Well, I guess we know what she was building now.
激活武器
Activate weapons.
我的天!
Jesus Christ!
教练 有什么办法?
Coach, any ideas?
我想你只可以硬熬过去了
You just have to tough it out, I guess.
收视率上去后 轩尼诗会把它收回去的
Hennessey will take it off after she's pumped up the ratings.
你肯定吗?
You sure about that?
那东西到底要去哪里?
Where the hell is that thing going?
该死!
妈的
Fuck me.
管事婆
Lists.
收到
Receiving.
我要你帮我接到另外那台车上
I want you to patch me through to another car.
好的
On it.
乔?
Joe?
是谁?
Who is this?
我是弗兰克 你想怎么样?
It's Frank. What do you want?
我们玩场进攻游戏如何?
How about we play a little offense?
希望你知道自己在做什么
I hope you know what you're doing.
那才像娱乐节目
Now that's entertainment!
他妈的!
Damn it!
弗兰克斯坦 弗兰克斯坦! 弗兰克斯坦!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
弗兰克斯坦 弗兰克斯坦!
Frankenstein! Frankenstein!
丑八怪 反应挺快的
Nice reflexes there, lgor.
赛车手的敏捷反应
Race car reflexes.
兄弟 你看起来很困惑
You look lost, pal.
这次不是
Not this time.
我感觉到你跟弗兰克很像
I got this feeling that you and Frank are close.
非常的像
Real close.
就算是那种怪口音 你们听起来都很像
That weird accent. You even kind of sound alike.
我在想 如果你出了意外会怎么样呢?
I was wondering, what if you got in a accident?
弗兰克会不会因此不能参赛呢?
Would that throw Frank off his game a little bit?
我表示怀疑
I doubt it,
他是一个丧心病狂
sick, fucked-up guy that he is.
可能他只是想杀了你
He might just want to kill you.
酷
That's cool.
那我猜我一会能见到他
So I guess I'll see him later.
对吗?
Right?
我们撤
Let's roll.
夫人 冒昧问一句 我们打算怎么做?
Ma'am, with all respect, what are we going to do?
当然 我们要干掉他
We're going to kill him, of course.
你要我杀了弗兰克斯坦?
You want me to kill Frankenstein?
别傻了
Don't be stupid.
弗兰克斯坦死不了的
Frankenstein can't die.
毕竟 他只是一副面具
After all, he's just a mask.
今晚是死亡飞车的最后一场
Tonight is the final leg of the Death Race,
很有可能会诞生新的冠军
and perhaps a new champion will arise.
五场比赛的赢家
A five times winner.
首个获得自由的人
The first man ever to gain his freedom.
这个世界把你们交给我 因为你们不适合成为它的一份子
The world gave you to me because you were not fit to be a part of it.
你们不适合当丈夫
You were not fit to be husbands,
不适合当父亲
you were not fit to be fathers,
和别人一起生活时会严重威胁到别人
and were too dangerous to live with the rest of us.
什么狗屁?
What is this shit, man?
但今晚你们比赛时
But when you race tonight,
记住全世界的目光都落在你们身上
know that the eyes of the world are upon you.
记住那个曾经拒绝过你们的世界
And know that the very same world which rejected you
他们的心跳呼吸都由你们掌握着
now lives and breathes with you.
因你们的勇气而感动
And it draws inspiration from your courage.
还没有人赢过五场比赛
No one is ever gonna win five races.
所以 好好比赛
So race well...
没人能走出这里
Nobody is ever getting out of here.
记着 我把你们都奉为我的英雄
...and know that I consider you all my heroes.
给你看些东西
I want to show you something.
杀不死我的 杀不死我的 我是他妈的的死神
Can't kill me. Can't kill me. I'm the fucking Reaper.
你们可以烧我
You can burn me.
你们可以射我 但你们就是他妈的...
You can shoot me. But you can't motherfucking...
那里
There.
炮手 管事婆
Gunner, Lists.
如果我加个半加仑的储备油箱
Will Hennessey's inspectors care
轩尼诗的检查员会在意吗?
if we had a haIf gallon reserve tank?
加个半加仑的?
Another haIf gallon?
你的油箱已经能装35加仑了
You got a fuel tank that holds 35 gallons.
你要多那半加仑干什么?
What the hell you want another haIf gallon for?
教练?
Coach?
给他想要的
Let's give the man what he wants.
你要去哪里?
Hey, where are you going?
噢 情况不妙
Oh, this is not good.
够大胆的 来踩场
Real brave, coming over here.
我要赢得比赛 我要离开这粪坑
I'm going to win this race, 'Cause I want out of this shithole.
我已经赢了三场了
I've already won three races.
再赢两场我就能在迈阿密抽雪茄王了
Two more, and I'm smoking Cohibas in Miami.
弗兰克可以考虑一下
Frank might want to think about that.
因为我走了
'Cause I'm gone.
离开这里了
Out of here.
或许才会轮到他
Then maybe it's his turn.
或许他在想这是另一条出路
Maybe he's thinking it's the other way around.
现在 滚出我的地盘
From here on out, you stay the fuck out of my pit.
嘿
Hey.
我想你应该跟弗兰克谈谈
Thinking you and Frank should have a little talk.
欢迎收看死亡飞车最后一场
Welcome to the final installment of Death Race.
7位车手丧生了
Seven men dead.
西亚德
Siad,
格林
Grimm,
柯尔特 派晨高
Colt, Pachenko,
卡森
Carson,
里金斯
Riggins
和14K都丧身了
and 14K are all dead.
只剩下弗兰克斯坦和大炮乔
Just Frankenstein and Machine Gun Joe survive.
弗兰克 为了他的自由而战
Frank, racing for his freedom.
乔 不惜一切阻止他
Joe, doing anything to stop him.
强强对抗 绝不怜惜
It's mano y mano, and there will be no mercy.
今晚 只有一个能活着走下赛道
Tonight, only one man will walk off this track alive.
收视已破7000万记录 加入一齐来吧
A record 70 million are already watching. Join them.
现在就订购最终决赛
Subscribe to the final stage now.
先生 能当你的领航真是荣幸
It's an honor to navigate for you, sir.
我叫做... 省省吧
They call me... Save it.
没时间去认识你
We won't have time to get acquainted.
那些是什么?
What the hell are those?
俄式7号火箭推进式榴弹
Model 7 Russian states armory RPG's.
可穿透装甲 自动上弹 精确射程达到1000码
Armor-piercing, self-arming, accurate to 1,000 yards.
我也这么想
That's what I thought.
囚犯 退后
Prisoner, step back.
我想这对你来说是点鼓励
I thought maybe you could use a little inspiration.
你的释放令
Your release papers.
已经签好了
They're already signed.
你要做的就是活着走下赛道
All you have to do is walk off that track alive.
当然 也要赢
Well, and win, of course.
但如果你真的赢了
But if you do win,
我希望你能考虑留下来
I want you to think about staying here.
继续做弗兰克斯坦
As Frankenstein.
和我合作
With me.
嗯
Yeah.
我看得出你的恳求
I can see the appeal.
你要自由来干什么呢?
What would you do with your freedom?
回到你女儿身边?
Go back to your daughter?
我是这么想的
That's the idea.
问题是
The thing is,
你能带给她最好的将来吗?
are you really the best future she could possibly have?
你真的是做父亲的料吗?
Are you really daddy material?
或者事实上 你更适合做其他的?
Or deep down, are you something else?
如果你认定赛道才是你的归属
If you decided that out there on that track is where you belong,
那将会是我见过最无私的爱
it would be the most unselfish act of love I've ever seen.
好好考虑一下
Just something to think about.
这是什么?
What's this?
小改进
Small modification.
轩尼诗告诉我 当你快要赢时 我要阻止你
So Hennessey telIs me if you're going to win, I'm supposed to stop you.
是吗? 是
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
看来我们没什么优势
Sounds like the odds are stacked against us.
那尽你全力
Then do what you do best.
开车
Drive.
先生们 这场应该很有趣
Gentlemen, this should be interesting.
前面的宝剑亮了
Lit sword up ahead.
关闭它 长官?
Deactivate that. Sir?
听我说就可以了
Just do it.
重新打开
Switch it back on.
武器可以用了!
Weapons are up!
妈的!
Damn it!
操!
Shit.
前面的护盾亮了!
Lit shield up ahead!
妈的!
Damn it!
怎么呢?
What happened?
一定是轩尼诗关掉了 那婊子
Hennessey must have deactivated it. Bitch!
给我点烟
Light me up.
派对时间到了
It's party time.
教练 我们得弄点火药
Coach, we gotta get the firepower.
跑了半圈 什么都不亮给我们
Nothing lit for a haIf lap.
我们支持不了多久了
We won't last that long!
把墓碑卸下
Drop the tombstone.
什么?
What?
照做!
Do it!
听我指示 三
On my mark. Three,
二
two,
一!
one!
卸
Mark.
妈的!
Damn it!
白痴 我怎么会连续中两次计呢
That shit don't work twice, playboy!
妈的
Shit.
再过四分之一圈有护盾
Lit shield in quarter lap.
听到吗?再过四分之一圈有护盾
Do you hear that? Lit shield in the quarter lap.
他紧紧追着
He's coming up fast.
给护盾他们 让观众找点乐
Let them get the shield. Keep the viewers interested.
贱人 他拿到护盾了!
Son of a bitch! He got the shield!
装上炸药
Arm the explosive.
以防万一
Just in case.
嘿 弗兰克斯坦
Yo, Frankenfreak.
有件玩意
This villager's got a pitchfork,
正直冲向你的屁股
and it's headed straight up your ass.
发生什么事了?
What just happened?
耶 耶 弗兰克!
Yeah! Yeah, Frank!
他们跑出赛道外了 他们在逃跑
They're off the track. They're escaping.
他们朝桥那边逃去
They're headed for the bridge.
关闭他们的武器 打开电击开关
Their weapons. Hit the kill switches.
夫人 7000万观众 他们都在看着
Seventy million viewers, ma'am. They're all watching.
把直播关掉
Shut the webcast down.
关掉!
Shut it down!
把电脑关掉
Shut the fucking computers down now!
出去 出去 出去!
Get out! Get out! Get out! Now!
出去 出去!
Get out! Get out!
呦 弗兰克斯坦
Yo, Frankenstein.
真庆幸我们谈过
It's good we had that little talk.
我们给那婊子演了场好戏 是吗?
We gave that bitch a good show, huh?
给我!
Give me that!
好啊杂种 跟我玩
Okay, cocksucker, fuck with me,
看看最后谁更惨
and we'll see who shits on the sidewalk.
某人现在一定气疯了
Somebody's mad right now.
没人能搞我的车
Nobody fucks with my car.
混蛋!
Son of a bitch!
直升机行动
Get the choppers in the air!
赶快 起飞 快 快
Come on. Off the ground. Go, go, go!
你真名是什么?
So what's your real name?
没时间跟你闲聊
I don't have the time for small talk.
只是想知道我跟谁一起逃命
Just want to know who I'm riding with.
杰森·艾姆斯
Jensen Ames.
像... 像那款车
Like... Like the car.
像那款车
Like the car.
那 杰森·艾姆斯 我希望你已经心里有数了
Well, Jensen Ames, I hope you got a plan,
因为看起来 我们并不能逃很远
'Cause it's not like we're going to get very far.
你说得对
You're right.
我们不能
We won't.
现在是好时机
Now would be a good time.
改得真好
Very nice modification.
那额外的半加仑油缸
That extra haIf gallon reserve tank
应该能伴你度过难关了
should see you through to the finish.
一路顺风 弗兰克
Bon voyage, Frank.
夫人 直升机有图像了
Choppers have a visual, ma'am.
祝你好运 乔
Good luck, Joe.
帮我接到飞行员那里 我要马上跟他通话
Get me a pilot. I need to talk to a pilot right now.
好 接通了
Okay. You're on.
盯着弗兰克斯坦 别跟丢了
Stay with Frankenstein! Don't lose him.
你确定要这样做吗?
Sure you're up for this?
我确定
I'm sure.
是我欠弗兰克的
I owe it to Frank.
另外 轩尼诗已经签了我的释放令
Besides, Hennessey already gave me my release papers.
他们必须让我走
They have to let me out.
夫人 他们截住他了
They've stopped him, ma'am.
把手放在我们能见到的地方
Keep your hands where we can see them.
你被捕了
You are under arrest!
我重复 把手放在我们能见到的地方
I repeat, keep your hands where we can see them!
你被捕了
You are under arrest!
嘿 丑八怪 圣诞快乐
Hey, lgor. Merry Christmas.
来吧 我们一起离开这里
Come on. Let's get out of here.
漂亮
Nice.
你有这样的衣服
The fact you have duds like these
会令人怀疑你的
might make someone question your...
我的品味?
My taste?
对 可以这么说
Yeah. So to speak.
我不知道你有什么打算 但我要去迈阿密
I don't know about you, but I'm headed to Miami.
迈阿密不错啊
Miami's good.
我们那边见
I'll meet you down there.
我要回我的宝贝女儿后
Once I got my baby girl.
可惜没有机会收拾轩尼诗那婊子
It's a shame I didn't get to take care of that bitch Hennessey.
是啊真可惜
Yeah. That is a shame.
弗兰克斯坦被抓回来了
Frankenstein has been retrieved.
夫人 收视率创新高
And, ma'am, ratings are off the charts.
贺礼和贺辞已经到了
Gifts and congratulations are already coming in.
你又赢了
You win again.
里奇先生
Mr. Ulrich,
我总会赢
I always win.
见鬼去
Damn.
我真爱这游戏
I love this game.
(六个月后 2000英里外)
(墨西哥 圣罗萨利亚)
我们要修好这破车?
So we had to fix this car?
还要修多久?
How many times we gonna keep doing this, man?
这车不能起动了
This car is not gonna start.
妈的!
Damn it!
你说你要我做个老实人 对吗?
You say you want me to live the life of an honest man, huh?
对 你最好适应这种生活
Yep. You better get used to it.
嘿 丑八怪
Hey, lgor.
看来我们有个伴了
Think we got a little company.
为什么那么久?
What took you so long?
证明我的释放令时遇到些麻烦
Had trouble getting my release papers approved.
等等 我想让你见个人
Wait here. There's someone I want you to meet.
看看她
Look at her.
多美的眼睛
She has beautiful eyes.
像她妈妈
They're her mother's.
车哪儿弄来的?
Where'd you get the rims?
打牌赢的
I won it. Card game.
是吗?
Yeah, right.
真的
No, really.
这引擎有多大马力?
How many horsepower's in this engine?
500匹
Five hundred.
你肯定吗?
You sure about that?
曾经有人问我
Someone once asked me,
我能不能为我女儿带来美好的将来
did I think I was the best future for my little girl?
这问题我想了很久
Something I've thought about for a long time.
最后我想通了
This is what I decided.
这世界上没有人是完美的 我当然不是
No one in this world is perfect. Heaven knows I'm not.
但我爱她胜于任何人
But I love her more than anyone else possibly could.
到最后 这才是最重要的
In the end, that's all that matters.
她是我新生活的希望 更美好的生活
She's my chance at something else. Something better.
而我绝不会放弃
And there's no way I'm letting go of that.
好啊 杂种 跟我玩
Okay, cocksucker, fuck with me,
看最后谁更惨
and we'll see who shits on the sidewalk.